So in the previous video we have seen how to upload the file using STB program into STM eight microcontroller.
In this video we are going to see how to make a USB two connection with MFC 5 to 2 module.
So we are going to use other header pins as you can see it over here.
The connection we made for STM eight microcontroller, we use this pins which are near to this crystal.
Right now we have to make a connection for USB to TTL, and with this connection we are going to do
all our related tasks like updating the blocks and updating the keys.
We are going to do through this connection.
Right, So this connection you have to make from test point, this is you can see the test point is
written over here and you have to make a connection for from here.
Right.
So this is a usb2 connection.
This connection is also very simple.
What you have to do is first you have to make 5 volt to 5 volt connection, right?
So there is a five volt written on the board as well as on the USB to USB.
Right.
So you have to make up five volt connection.
Then there is a ground connection after that.
And there are two other connections which are r, x and t x.
Now this is these are these two connections are cross connections, right?
So ground will go to ground and five volts will go to five volts but r x of board will go into the t
of USB to USB.
Right.
And the t of board will go into the r of this USB.
So it is a cross connection from the board will go into the t of USB and from the board will go into
the r of USB.
So you have to remember that and make a connection and you can see the connection in the video as well
over here.
Right.
So this is the correction.
Now, let's just see this in action.
So let me move into my machine.
So our board is connected from USB to device.
And this is the software.
It's RC 522 manager.
So let's just double click on it and you will get this software from the resources which I have provided
before, right?
So all you have to do is first you have to select the serial port over here.
And you can refresh it after making a connection and the serial port will be visible in the select box,
you have to select it and make it open.
And to test it, you just have to press normal.
And to close the connection, you just have to close it, right?
So right now I haven't placed any card on it, so we cannot do any read or write operation.
In the next video, we are going to see how to write data blocks.
Then we will also see how to write Keys Key A and key B on sector trailer.
After that, we will see the how to create the value blocks, right?
So all the things which we have covered in 1 to 2 module, we will cover it over here as well.
Before continuing in this section, I would recommend that you should go through that 1 to 2 section
as well, because I have covered Mifare classic concepts in very detail in that section.
Right.
So I'm not going to cover that details again in this section.
All I'm going to do is I'm just going to go through how to write and update the blocks through this
software, right?
So we will specifically target this software in this section.
So in the next video, we are going to see how to read and write data blocks.